just shoot for the stars,If it feels right
射下星星，如果这样感觉不错
And then from my heart, If you feel like
然后摘取我心，如果你愿意
You take me away
你带我离开
You make it okay
因你让这一切变美好
I swear I’ll behave
我发誓我会安分守己
You wanted control
你曾想要控制
So we waited
所以我们等待
I put on a show
我总是在演出
Now we’re naked
但现在赤诚相待
You say I’m a kid
你说我是一个孩子
My ego is bare
自尊又好胜
I don’t give a shit! And it goes like this
但我不在乎了，所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
With the moves like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o
你失控，我失控
Well maybe it’s hard
是的，也许这很困难
When you feel like You’re broken and scarred
当你觉得你受到了伤害
It feels right
但是你会感觉好起来的
When you’re with me
当你和我在一起
I’ll make you believe
我会让你坚信
I’ve got the key
我有神奇之钥
Oh, so get in the car, You can ride it,Oh
我们进车里去吧，今天你可以开
Wherever you want Get inside it
无论你想要去哪里，交由你决定
If you wanna steer
如果你想要掌舵
I’m shifting gears
我就立刻换你
I’ll take it from here
从现在就开始
And it goes like this…
所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the mooo ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
With the moves like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the m ooo ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
You wanna know,how to make me smile
你想要知道如何逗我笑？
Take control on me just for the night
这个夜晚你来掌控大局
When I share my secret, You’re gonna have to keep it
你要保守和你分享的秘密
Nobody else can see this
没有人可以知道
So watch and learn I won't show you twice
所以为什么不呢？
Head to toe
从头到尾，原原本本
ooh baby roll me right
我要说给你听
But if i share my secret, You’re gonna have to keep it
你要保守和你分享的秘密
Nobody else can see this
没有人可以知道
Oh! And it goes like this…
所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the mo  come on say
你失控，我失控   一起唱
o oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo ves like jagger
我们一起失控
How dare you say that my behavior is unacceptable
你怎能说我的行为令人无法接受
So condescending unnecessarily critical
如此不必要的屈尊带有批评的意味
I have the tendency of getting very physical
我有动粗的意向
So watch your step cause if I do you'll need a miracle
所以小心 因为一旦我采取行动你将需要奇迹(来解救自己)
You drain me dry and make me wonder why I'm even here
你将我慢慢耗干 让我不明白为什么自己还在这里
This Double Vision I was seeing is finally clear
过去不曾看清的模糊景象最终也变得清晰
You want to stay but you know very well I want you gone
你想留下但你很清楚其实我想让你离开
Not fit to funkin' tread the ground I'm walking on
我不想再这样惊恐的走下去
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
What you are doing is screwing things up inside my head
你做的事情让我感到紧张
You should know better you never listened to a word I said
你最好知道我所说的你一句都没有听进去
Clutching your pillow and writhing in a naked sweat
抓紧枕头因痛苦而扭动身体
Hoping somebody someday will do you like I did
希望有一天会有人像我这样对待你
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
Is there anyone out there
有人吗
Kill does it burn
灼伤会死人吗
Is it painful to learn
了解它很痛苦吗
That it's me that has all the control
那就是可以掌控一切的我
Thrill does it sting
刺你会紧张吗
When you feel what I bring
当你感受到我所带来的
And you wish that you had me to hold
你会希望你有我来支撑
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
我感觉很好，你们好吗？！
能这里表演心情十分激动 谢谢你们
里约大会场！
接下来的这首歌  稍等片刻
先来介绍我们的Jesse Carmicheal (作曲)
Sunday morning rain is falling
星期天的早晨下着细雨
Steal some covers share some skin
天空被遮蔽
Clouds are shrouding us in moments unforgettable
乌云在这难忘的时刻笼罩着我们
You twist to fit the mold that I am in
你愿改变自己来适应我
But things just get so crazy living life gets hard to do
可以一切都难以控制 生活越来越糟
And I would gladly hit the road get up and go if I knew
我愿意起身上路
That someday it would lead me back to you
如果我知道有一天我会回到你身边
回到你身边
That may be all I need
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with me
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow on Sunday morning
悠闲的星期天早晨
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开
My ingers trace your every  outline
手指轻拂你的酮体
Make a picture with my hands
我的手指绘下一幅地图
Back and forth we sway like branches in a storm
我们像风中的枝叶一样摇摆
Change the weather still together when it ends
四季变化 我们一直相伴
That may be all I need.Come on
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with me
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow on Sunday morning
缓缓的星期天早晨
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开
You twist to fit
你愿改变自己来适应我
gets hard to do
生活越来越糟
Sunday morning rain
星期天早晨的雨
And I would get up to you baby
我会回到你身边的
it would lead me back to you
有一天我会回到你身边
Find the way get myself  back home to you
回到你身边
That may be all i need
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with mebaby
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow
悠闲的
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开
让我听到你们的声音里也人民
一二    一二三
Now as the summer fades, I let you slip away
现在，随着夏季的褪色，我让你离开
You say I'm not your type, but I can make you sway
你说我不是你的适合类型，但我可以让你选择
It makes you burn to learn that you're not the only one
你难受的知道你并不是我的唯一
I'd let you be if you put down your blazin' gun
如果你放下（高贵），我会让你做自己
Now you've gone somewhere else, far away
现在，你已经有别的地方，远离我的地方
I don't know if I will find you (find you, find you)
我不知道是否能够找到你（找到你，找到你）
But you feel my breath on your neck
但是我感觉我的呼吸仍留在你的颈部
Can't believe I'm right behind you (right behind you)
不敢相信我就在你的身后（在你后面）
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Sometimes you move so well it's hard not to give in
有时候你那么好，（让我）很难不对你妥协
I'm lost, I can't tell where you end and I begin
我迷失了，我不知道你是怎么结束的而我又是怎么开始的
It makes me burn to learn you're with another man
当我知道你与另一男子在一起，我心如焚烧
I wonder if he's half the lover that I am
我不知道他是否有我一半的好
Now you've gone somewhere else, far away
现在，你已经有别的地方，远离我的地方
I don't know if I will find you (find you, find you)
我不知道是否能够找到你（找到你，找到你）
But you feel my breath on your neck
但是我感觉我的呼吸仍留在你的颈部
Can't believe I'm right behind you (right behind you)
不敢相信我就在你的身后（在你后面）
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Baby, baby, please believe me
宝贝，宝贝，请相信我
Find it in your heart to reach me
找到我在你心里的位置
Promise not to leave me behind
答应我不要离开我
Take me down but take it easy
记住我但是放轻松
Make me think but don't decieve me
让我觉得你没有欺骗我
Torture me by taking your time
占用你时间相当于对我实施酷刑
Cause  you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get to me got to me
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
现在 里也的观众
我要看到你们的手 能举起来吗
我需要你们 一起唱吗？“欧耶---欧耶”
唱 “耶耶---耶耶”
So scared of breaking it
害怕我们之间出现问题
But you won't let it bend
而你却不想重复以前的尴尬
And I wrote two hundred letters
我写了两百封 解释为什么
I won't ever send
但却一封也没寄出去
Somehow it is cut so much  Deeper then they seem
感觉到不幸如同头上剑
You'd rather cover up I'd rather let them be
你再怎么掩饰 但米已成炊
So let me be And I'll set you free
那就随便 我还你自由吧
I am in misery There ain't no other Who can comfort me
经历过非人痛苦 谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me? Your silence is slowly killing me
干嘛不直接点 这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Your salty skin and how It mixes in with mine
你的痛苦跟我比小巫见大巫
The way it feels to be Completely intertwined
紧紧深陷 纠葛难以摆脱
It's not that I didn't care It's that I didn't know
不是我不在乎 是我从没有这样想过
It's not what I didn't feel, It's what I didn't show
So let me be And I'll set you free
那就随便 我还你自由吧
I am in misery There ain't no other
经历过非人痛苦
Who can comfort me
谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me?
干嘛不直接点
Your silence is slowly killing me
这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad  You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Say your faith is shaken You may be mistaken
你说你可能只是一时糊涂
You keep me wide awake and
不是没有机会和你在一起
Waiting for the sun
我就知道
I'm desperate and confu sed
我挺而走险
So far away from you
糊里糊涂远离你
I'm getting here
算了 我要回到你身边
Don't care where I have to go
你别管我做什么事
Why do you do what you do to me, yeah
为什么 为什么你还要折磨我
Why won't you answer me, answer me yeah
干嘛不直接点
Why do you do what you do to me yeah
为什么 为什么你还要折磨我
Why won't you answer me, answer me yeah
干嘛不直接点
I am in misery There ain't no other
经历过非人痛苦
Who can comfort me
谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me?
干嘛不直接点
Your silence is slowly killing me
这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
I wake up with blood-shot eyes
我睁开我喷血的眼睛醒过来
Struggled to memorize
拼命去记忆
The way it felt between your thighs
那被你的一切包围的感觉
Pleasure that made you cry
还有那些高兴得令我想哭的事情
Feels so good to be bad
变坏的感觉真好
Not worth the aftermath, after that
不用管结果，在那之后
After that, try to get you back
在那之后，我就要努力把你抢回来
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
So this is goodbye
而这就是离别
God damn I'm standing here
他妈的我站在这里
Decisions that made my bed
决定去整整我的床
Now I must lay in it
我现在必须去整理它了
And deal with things I left unsaid
要处理那些我没说的东西……
I want to dive into you
我想跳到你那儿去
Forget what you're going through
忘记你所经历过的那些事
I get behind, make your move
我在后面，让你动起来
Forget the truth
忘记事实
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
So this is goodbye  waiting me
而这就是离别  跟着我
I've been here before
我来过这里
One day a week
每周来一次
And it won't hurt anymore
而这已经不会让我感到难过了
You caught me in a lie
你识破了我的谎言
I got no alibi
我没什么借口
Why you said you had a meeting
你却以会议为借口
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
So this is goodbye
而这就是离别
非常感谢大家！
我滴天啊
大家  看看这场面 大家转身看看这一切
在继续之前 我想说
我们很感激 非常感谢大家 我们很感动
非常开心和荣幸能在这里演出
感谢大家 接下来将演唱第一张专辑的歌“太阳”  希望你们喜欢
说：一 二 和 三  开始
After school Walking home
放学后走在回家的路上
Fresh dirt under my fingernails
新鲜的泥土还留在我的指甲中
I can smell hot asphalt
我仿佛可以闻到热沥青的味道
Cars screech to a halt to let me pass
汽车都停了下来给我让路
And I cannot remember
我不记得
What life was like through photographs
照片中的我当时是怎样生活的
Trying to recreate images life gives us from our past
我一直在尝试回到过去的生活中去
And sometimes it's a sad song
有时它是一曲悲歌
But I cannot forget
但是我不能忘却
Refuse to regret So glad I met you
拒绝遗憾痛惜 遇见你我很快乐
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles from the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
Moving on down my street
顺着街道前行
I see people I won't ever meet
许多陌生人和我擦肩而过
I think of her, take a breath
我想着她 深呼吸
Feel the beat in the rhythm of my steps
感觉好像有什么东西打乱了我的节奏
And sometimes its a sad song
有时它就如一首悲歌
But I cannot forget
但我无法忘却
Refuse to regret
拒绝遗憾
So glad I met you
很高兴遇见你
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles from the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
I can feel severa,I can feel the warm
我能感受到太阳到来的温暖
女士们，先生们  在另一边有请詹姆斯为我们演奏吉他
The rhythm of the conversation
甜美的声音
The perfection of her creation
是她完美的创造
The sex she slipped into my coffee
那熟悉的场景出现在我的脑海中
The way she felt when she first saw me
那是当我们第一次相遇时
Hate to love and love to hate her
不想再去爱了 但却因此爱上了恨
Like a broken record player
如同一个老旧了的唱机一样
Back and forth and here and gone
翻来覆去
and on and on and on and on
一直这样下去
But I cannot forget
但我无法忘却
Refuse to regret
拒绝遗憾
So glad I met you
很高兴遇见你
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles form the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
谢谢大家
下一首歌 我觉得 是一首反映离家之苦的歌
再来一次
我的失误，唱低了，我错了
我们再试一次  试试这个调
谢谢 唱得太棒了 非常感谢！
I asked her to stay
我请她留下
But she wouldn't listen
但她不会听的
She left before I had the chance to say
在我有机会表达之前她已离开了
The words that were mend
弥补的言辞
the things that were broken
破碎的一切
But now its far too late she's gone away
但现在一切都太晚了，她早已离开
Every night you cry yourself to sleep
每天泪水伴你入睡
Thinking why does this happen to me
思量着为什么自己这么倒霉
Why does every moment have to be so hard
为什么美时每刻都是这么痛苦
Hard to believe that
难以相信这些
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
The taste of her breath, I'll never get over
永远也忘不了曾经感受到她呼吸的那一刻
And the noises that she make keep me awake
她的吵闹声此刻令我清醒
The weight of things that remain unspoken
事情的重要性仍然未知
Built up so much it crushed us everyday
用心的构建却让我们每一天都觉得身心疲惫
Every night you cry yourself to sleep
每晚泪水伴你入睡
Thinking why does this happen to me
思量着为什么自己这么倒霉
Why does every moment have to be so hard
为什么每时每刻都是这么痛苦
Hard to believe that
难以相信这些
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
Of all the things I felt I've never really showed
我没能将所有的一切都告诉你
perhaps the worst is that I ever let you go
但是最糟糕的是我居然曾经让你离开
should not ever let you go oh oh oh
我本不该让你走的，噢
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
谢谢大家
我们之前没来这里表演过 你们还要更多吗？！
I didn't hear what you were saying
我不想听到你说什么
I live on raw emotion baby
宝贝，我的感情并不成熟
I answer questions never maybe
我也许无法回答那些问题
And I'm not kind if you betray me
不过如果你背叛了我，我绝对不会客气
So who the hell are you to save me
你从地狱拯救了我
I never would have made it babe
我不会让别人得到你
If you needed love
在你需要爱的时候
Well then ask for love
请你去追寻它
Could have given love
我渴望得到爱
Now I'm taking
那么此时此刻我得到了爱
And it's not my fault
这并不是我的错
Cause you both deserve
为了你什么都值得
What's coming now
当它来临的时候
So don't say a word
就不要说什么
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
Don't you care about me? I don't think so
不关心我了吗？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here? I don't think so
我不认为他还会来到这里
Would have bled to make you happy
流出来的血液会使你感到开心么
You didn't need to treat me that (way)
你没有必要这样做
And now you beat me at my own game
你可以对我感到不满
And now I'm finally sleeping soundly
现在我终于可以安心了
And your lover's screaming loudly I hear a sound and hit the ground
你的爱人在尖叫声中倒在了地面
If you needed love
在你需要爱的时候
Well then ask for love
请你去追寻它
Could have given love
我渴望得到爱
Now I'm taking love
那麽此时此刻我得到了爱
And it's not my fault
这并不是我的错
Cause you both deserve
为了你什么都值得
What's coming now
当它来临的时候
So don't say a word
就不要说什么
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
Don't you care about me? I don't think so
不关心我了吗？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here?
他还会来到这里？
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕
I'm so sorry darling
我很抱歉，亲爱的
Did I do the wrong thing?
我到底做错了什么？
Oh, what was I thinking?
哦，我到底在想什么？
Is his heart still beating?
难道他的心仍在跳动？
Woah oh ohh
哇~~哦~~~哦~~
I don't feel so bad, I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕  我并不觉得糟糕
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
care about me? I don't think so
关心我？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here？I don't feel so bad
他还会来到这里？我并不觉得糟糕
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕
don't feel so bad
并不觉得糟糕
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕
Ohh I really need to know
哦，我真的需要知道
Ohh Ya gotta let me go
哦，你将让我走开
This time I really need to do things right
这次我必须正确的做好这件事情
Shivers that ya give me keep me freezing all night
战栗，为你让我整晚感到自己像是冻僵了一样
Shudder
颤栗
I can't believe it, I'm not myself
我不能相信，我不是我自己
suddenly I'm thinkin' of no one else
突然我不去想任何人
You make me shudder
你让我颤栗
Ohh I really need to know
哦，我真的需要知道
(Or else you) gotta let me go
否则就让我离去
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give me affection
给我你的爱慕之情
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter, stutter
你让我口吃，口吃
If I could touch you, I'd never let go
如果我可以碰触到你，我将永远不会放手
Now ya got me screaming and I cannot shut up, shut up
现在你让我尖叫，我难以停止，停止
Now I am lying on the bedroom floor barely even speaking
现在我躺在卧室地板上，甚至说话都感到困难
and I cannot get up, get up
我不能起来，起来
Ohh I really, I really, I really need to know
哦我真的，真的，我真的需要知道
Ya gotta let me go
你让我离开
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give me affection
给我你的爱慕之情
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter, stutter
你让我口吃，口吃
You knock me down, I can't get up, I'm stuck
你让我失望，我不能起来，我被困住了
Gotta stop shaking me up
停止吧，让我振作
I cant eat, cant sleep, can't think, .....
我饭不思，夜不寐，不能思考……
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give your attention
留给我一些关注
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter
你让我口吃
怎么唱？
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
非常好！
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
你们可以更大声的！
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
大家一起（唱）
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
再来一次
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
我需要你们全部人
每个人 都站起来
我要更多人  快点（站起来）
要听下一首吗   还要再听另外一首歌吗？
知道这首吗？跟着我们一起唱
开始了
I was so high
我是如此疯狂
I did not recognize
以至于没有察觉
The fire burning in her eyes
她眼里燃烧的火焰
The chaos that controlled my mind
混乱占据了我的思维
Whispered goodbye and she got on a plane
她轻声道别然后踏上飞机
Never to return again
从此一去不返
But always in my heart
但她永远在我心里
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore Come on
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别   一起唱
I tried my best to feed her appetite
我曾经努力的取悦她
Keep her coming every night
每晚让她高潮迭起
So hard to keep her satisfied
用尽全力让她感到满足
Kept playing love like it was just a game
她却把爱情当成游戏
Pretending to feel the same
这次又假装没有感觉
Then turn around and leave again
然后转身再度离去
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别
举起手来
I'll fix these broken things
我要弥补这所有的错
Repair your broken wings
修复你的折翼
And make sure everything's alright
让一切都好起来
Its all right.Its all right
没事的 会好的
My pressure on your hips
我在你臀上的压力
Sinking my fingertips
渗透我的指尖
Into every inch of you
进入你的每一寸肌肤
Cause I know that's what you want me to do
因为我知道你要我这样做
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
让我听到你的呐喊声 里也人民！
我要听到更多人的声音 再次呐喊吧
我滴天 谢谢你们 里也的观众
只是多么多么不可思议的经历啊！ 我们是魔力红 谢谢你们
晚安！
耶  把手举起来！
Put your hands, all over
把你的手,全部
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Put your hands, all over
把你的手,全部
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
I can't seem to find
我好象没有找到
The pretty little face I left behind
我遗失的可爱小脸
Wandered out on the open road
在路上徘徊
Looking for a better place to call home
寻找一个更好的地方打电话回家
Gave her a place to stay
给她一个栖身的地方
And she got up and ran away
她起身跑掉
Well now I've had enough
现在我已经受够了
Her pretty little face has torn me up
她可爱的笑脸已经把我撕碎
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Tell me everything
告诉我一切的事情
It's gonna be alright
一切都会很好
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please walk with me, walk with me
请与我同行,与我同行
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Now you've lost your mind
现在你在犹豫不决
The pretty little girl I left behind
我遗失的可爱小女孩
And now you're getting rough
现在你正处于艰难
But everybody knows you're not that tough
但是每个人都知道你没有那么坚强
Wandered out on the open road
路上徘徊
Looking for a place to call your own
寻找一个地方只为呼唤你
Scared to death of the road ahead
害怕路的前方的死亡
Pretty little thing, don't get upset
可爱的小东西,不要不安
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Tell me everything
告诉我一切的事情
It's gonna be alright
一切都会很好
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please walk with me, walk with me
请与我同行,与我同行
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
So come down off your cloud
所以从你的云朵上下来
Say it now
现在就说
Say it loud
大声的说
Get up in my face
在我的期盼中振作
Pretty little girl
可爱的小女孩
Come make my day
过来让我开心
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Now walk with me, walk with me now
请与我同行,与我同行
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Gotta talk to me, talk to me
跟我说话,跟我说话
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Gotta walk with me, walk with me
跟我说话,跟我说话
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Love is a game you said
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Yeah
耶~
欧耶！ 谢谢
所以 女士们 先生们
能在这里表演是一件很荣幸的事情 因为
今晚还有其他好多很棒的嘉宾在这演出
例如酷玩乐队待会会出来表演  多么棒啊
能在这里成为（音乐节）表演的一部分是多么酷啊  再说一次
非常感谢大家
剩下最后一首歌 一首 你们想听吗？
这首歌 这首歌是描述女孩的歌 现场的女孩们在哪里？
有一个漂亮、超凡、性感的女孩  这首歌讲的就是这个
beauty queen of only eighteen she
仅仅18岁而美丽的小女王
had some trouble with herself
她自己内心有些烦恼
he was always there to help her
他总是会在守候着去帮助她
she always belonged to someone else
但她总是一直属于别人
i drove for miles and miles
我驾着车子 走了许多路程
and wound up at your door
终于来到你的家门前
i've had you so many times but somehow i want more
虽然我已经与你在一齐好几次  我想需要你的更多爱
i don't mind spending everyday
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *2
她会拥有我的爱
tap on my window, knock on my door
轻叩我的窗口 轻敲我的门
i want to make you feel beautiful
我只想令你觉得一切都美好
i know i tend to get so insecure
我知道我不太成熟
it doesn't matter anymore
那完全不要紧
it's not always rainbows and butterflies
世上不会总是有彩虹和蝴蝶
it's compromise that moves us along
这使到我们不断向前行
my heart is full and my door's always open
我的心和我的门总是为你打开
you can come anytime you want
只要你想的话 你就随时能来
i don't mind spending everyday
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
i know where you hide
我知道你在哪里
alone in your car
独自在你的车中
know all of the things
知道一切
that make you who you are
晓得令你变成如此的一切
i know that goodbye
我也知道再见
means nothing at all
并不意味什么
comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls
在她每次失落时都能安慰她
yeah!tap on my window, knock on my door
轻叩我的窗口 轻敲我的门
i want to make you feel beautiful
我只想令你觉得一切都美好
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
我知道现场有很多人
大家来个大合唱
这首歌剩下的部分 你跟我一起唱吗？
我不会讲巴西语 但我尽量用英语解释
我要从这里对半分成
一.二，两个队
这边的观众！
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
漂亮  你们太棒了！
等一下   这边的观众！
开始   大声点，大声点
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
这边的
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
and she will be loved she will...
告诉她我对她的心意
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
and she woll...i don't mind spending every day
她会...我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
一 二 三  唱！
pleas don't try so hard to say goodbye
请别太快说再见
大家一起来
and she will be loved
她会拥有我的爱
我们永远都不会忘记这里的 谢谢大家
享受接下来酷玩乐队的表演
谢谢 我们是魔力红 晚安！